{
  "problems": [
    {
      "problem": "Reverse a String",
      "solution": "function hackTheString(encryptionKey) {\n  let decryptedString = '';\n  for (let i = encryptionKey.length - 1; i >= 0; i--) {\n    decryptedString += encryptionKey[i];\n  }\n  return decryptedString;\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Factorialize a Number",
      "solution": "function breachFactorialLockdown(securityCode) {\n  if (securityCode < 0) {\n    return -1;\n  } else if (securityCode === 0) {\n    return 1;\n  } else {\n    let bypassCode = 1;\n    for (let i = 1; i <= securityCode; i++) {\n      bypassCode *= i;\n    }\n    return bypassCode;\n  }\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Check for Palindromes",
      "solution": "function infiltratePalindromeDetection(encryptionProtocol) {\n  let decryptedProtocol = encryptionProtocol.toLowerCase().replace(/[^a-z0-9]/g, '');\n  let decryptedReverse = decryptedProtocol.split('').reverse().join('');\n  return decryptedProtocol === decryptedReverse;\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Find the Longest Word in a String",
      "solution": "function crackLongestWord(mainframeData) {\n  let longestWordExtraction = 0;\n  let breachWords = mainframeData.split(' ');\n  for (let i = 0; i < breachWords.length; i++) {\n    if (breachWords[i].length > longestWordExtraction) {\n      longestWordExtraction = breachWords[i].length;\n    }\n  }\n  return longestWordExtraction;\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Return Largest Numbers in Arrays",
      "solution": "function bypassArrayFirewall(hackedArrays) {\n  let maxNumbersRetrieved = [];\n  for (let i = 0; i < hackedArrays.length; i++) {\n    let max = hackedArrays[i][0];\n    for (let j = 1; j < hackedArrays[i].length; j++) {\n      if (hackedArrays[i][j] > max) {\n        max = hackedArrays[i][j];\n      }\n    }\n    maxNumbersRetrieved.push(max);\n  }\n  return maxNumbersRetrieved;\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Confirm the Ending",
      "solution": "function decryptEndingCode(encryptionCode, targetCode) {\n  return encryptionCode.slice(-targetCode.length) === targetCode;\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Repeat a String Repeat a String",
      "solution": "function executeRepeatLoop(encryptedString, loopCounter) {\n  let repeatedString = '';\n  while (loopCounter > 0) {\n    repeatedString += encryptedString;\n    loopCounter--;\n  }\n  return repeatedString;\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Truncate a String",
      "solution": "function hackTruncate(mainframeData, maxCharacters) {\n  return mainframeData.length > maxCharacters ? mainframeData.slice(0, maxCharacters) + '...' : mainframeData;\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Finders Keepers",
      "solution": "function findValuableData(mainframeData, accessFunction) {\n  return mainframeData.find(accessFunction);\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Boo who",
      "solution": "function hackBooleanFirewall(breachConfirmation) {\n  return typeof breachConfirmation === 'boolean';\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Slice and Splice",
      "solution": "function manipulateSlicedData(initialData, alteredData, insertionPoint) {\n  let modifiedData = alteredData.slice();\n  modifiedData.splice(insertionPoint, 0, ...initialData);\n  return modifiedData;\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Falsy Bouncer",
      "solution": "function bypassFalsyFilter(hackedData) {\n  return hackedData.filter(Boolean);\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Where do I Belong",
      "solution": "function infiltrateDataIndex(hackedData, targetData) {\n  return hackedData.concat(targetData).sort((a, b) => a - b).indexOf(targetData);\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Mutations",
      "solution": "function modifyData(securityBreachData) {\n  const [primaryData, secondaryData] = securityBreachData.map(hackedString => hackedString.toLowerCase());\n  return secondaryData.split('').every(decryptedChar => primaryData.includes(decryptedChar));\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Chunky Monkey",
      "solution": "function manipulateDataChunks(mainframeData, chunkSize) {\n  let modifiedData = [];\n  for (let i = 0; i < mainframeData.length; i += chunkSize) {\n    modifiedData.push(mainframeData.slice(i, i + chunkSize));\n  }\n  return modifiedData;\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Sum All Numbers in a Range",
      "solution": "function hackTheNumbers(securityBreach) {\n  let [min, max] = [...securityBreach].sort((a, b) => a - b);\n  return (max - min + 1) * (min + max) / 2;\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Diff Two Arrays",
      "solution": "function breachArraySecurity(dataArray1, dataArray2) {\n  return dataArray1.filter(item => !dataArray2.includes(item)).concat(dataArray2.filter(item => !dataArray1.includes(item)));\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Seek and Destroy",
      "solution": "function infiltrateAndDestroy(dataArray, ...targetData) {\n  return dataArray.filter(item => !targetData.includes(item));\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Wherefore art thou",
      "solution": "function identifyTarget(collectionData, targetSource) {\n  let accessKeys = Object.keys(targetSource);\n  return collectionData.filter(obj => accessKeys.every(key => obj.hasOwnProperty(key) && obj[key] === targetSource[key]));\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Reverse an Array",
      "solution": "function hackReverseArray(dataArray) {\n  let reversedDataArray = [];\n  for (let i = dataArray.length - 1; i >= 0; i--) {\n    reversedDataArray.push(dataArray[i]);\n  }\n  return reversedDataArray;\n}"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Find the Missing Letter",
      "solution": "function detectMissingLetter(encryptionData) {\n  for (let i = 0; i < encryptionData.length - 1; i++) {\n    if (encryptionData.charCodeAt(i + 1) - encryptionData.charCodeAt(i) > 1) {\n      return String.fromCharCode(encryptionData.charCodeAt(i) + 1);\n    }\n  }\n  return undefined;\n}"
    }
    ]
  }
  